Guide to the David Richmond Gergen Papers, 1964-1999 (bulk 1971-1992) RL.00443
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession (2000-0415)
  - SR 16 cont. (Box 35)
    - Sen. Robb, Charles (Box 35)
    - Rodgers, Dr. T.J. (Box 35)
    - Quayle, Dan, 2 folders (Box 35)
    - Pratt-Dixon, Sharon (Box 35)
    - Prestowitz, Clyde (Box 35)
    - Pushkov, Alexei (Box 35)
  - [SR 41?] (Box 35)
    - Campaigning - Negative (Box 35)
    - Canada (Box 35)
    - Capital Gains (Box 35)
    - Campaign -1992, 2 folders (Box 35)
    - Campaign Finance (Box 35)
    - Aspen Institute, 2 folders (Box 35)
    - Business and Schools (Box 35)
    - Bush (Box 35)
    - Bush - For Policy (Box 35)
    - The State of America's Children (book) (Box 35)
    - Presidential Campaign, 2 folders (Box 35)
    - Domestic Strategy Group (Box 35)
    - Changing Our Ways (Box 35)
    - Carnegie Endowment (Box 35)
    - Carnegie Report - Memo to Pres-Elect (Box 35)
    - Carnegie Commission, 2 folders (Box 35)
  - SR 13 (Box 36)
    - Children's Defense Fund (Box 36)
    - Children, 2 folders (Box 36)
    - Centel Corp. (Box 36)
    - Center for Naval Analyses (Box 36)
    - Charity (Box 36)
  - DRG 8 (Box 36)
    - Schedule/Events Files,1996 January-1997 December
      - Chemical Manufacturers, 1996 November 14 (Box 36)
      - Washington Campus, 1996 November 19 (Box 36)
      - Council of State Govt. Cleveland, 1996 December 9 (Box 36)
      - December 2 - USA Today Editorial Board (Box 36)
      - Southern Electric Exchange, Boca Raton, 1997 April 5 (Box 36)
      - Business Higher Education Forum, 1997 February 14 (Box 36)
      - Support our Students, 1997 March 13 (Box 36)
      - Canterbury School / Ft. Wayne Bank 1997 February 12-1997 February 13 (Box 36)
      - Pension Real Estate Assn., 1997 March 13 (Box 36)
      - Domestic Strategy Group, Portland, OR, March 14-March 16 (Box 36)
      - SOARI Dinner, Washington, D.C., 1996 December 16 (Box 36)
      - Santa Rosa Memorial Hospital, 1997 April 30 (Box 36)
      - Smithsonian Council Meeting, Washington, D.C., Octomber 31-November 2 (Box 36)
      - Haynsworth, Baldwin, Myrtle Beach, 1996 November 8 (Box 36)
      - Ervin, Cohen, Beverly Hills, CA, 1996 November 12 (Box 36)
      - Washington University, St. Louis, MO, 1996 November 13 (Box 36)
      - Harvard University, Kennedy Schook, Cambridge, 1996 November 7 (Box 36)
      - U.S. News Ad Sales Mtg, Atlantic City, September 29-Octomber 2 (Box 36)
      - Young Executives, Aspen Institute, Octomber 1 (Box 36)
      - Hitachi, Amelia Island, FL, 1991 Octomber 23 (Box 36)
      - Moravian College, Bethlehem, PA, 1996 Octomber 8 (Box 36)
      - Conference Board in NYC, 1996 Octomber 11 (Box 36)
      - Museum of the South, Sally Robinson, 1996 Octomber 14 (Box 36)
      - Mercer University, Georgia, 1996 Octomber 22 (Box 36)
      - Direct Marketing Association, New Orleans, Octomber 28 (Box 36)
      - Jones Day 1996 Octomber 15 (Box 36)
      - American Land Title Association, Los Angeles, 1996 Octomber 17 (Box 36)
      - Yale Alumni Octomber 25-Octomber 26 (Box 36)
      - Progress and Freedom Foundation Forum, 1996 August 5 (Box 36)
      - Society of Plastics, McLean, VA, 1996 September 26 (Box 36)
      - Yale Corporation Retreat September 27-September 29 (Box 36)
      - The CIT Group, LaQuinta, CA, 1996 September 28 (Box 36)
      - Aspen Institute Annual Dinner, NYC, 1996 Octomber 10 (Box 36)
      - DG's, Aspen CO, July 23-August 6 (Box 36)
      - American Hospital, Philly, PA, 1996 August 6 (Box 36)
      - SMU, Dallas, TX, 1996 August 10 (Box 36)
      - Aspen, Domestic Strategy Group, August17-August 21 (Box 36)
      - Innovations in Government Award, Boston, September 5-September 6 (Box 36)
      - Bill Moyers Special, Columbus, OH, 1996 September 7 (Box 36)
      - Bank of America, Aspen, CO, 1996 June 28 (Box 36)
      - One Valley Bank, Charleston, WV, 1996 September 17 (Box 36)
      - Bankers Roundtable, 1996 September 20 (Box 36)
      - Bill Friday Event, 1996 September 24 (Box 36)
      - Deloitte and Touche, Naples, FL 1996 September 19 (Box 36)
      - Family Impact Seminar, 1996 July 18 (Box 36)
      - Olympics,1996 July 19-1996 July 22 (Box 36)
      - Anti-Def League, Las Vegas, NV, 1996 June 1 (Box 36)
      - Bank of America, San Francisco, 1996 June 6 (Box 36)
      - Catholic Health Association, San Antonio, TX, 1996 June 12 (Box 36)
      - SBC Warburg, London, England, 1996 June 13 (Box 36)
      - Baldwin Wallace, 1996 June 8 (Box 36)
      - Duke Fuqua School, 1996 June 20 (Box 36)
      - U of Minnesota, 1996 May 1 (Box 36)
      - National Paper Trade, Las Vegas, May 1 (Box 36)
      - Donaldson and Co, Nassau, Bahamas, 1996 May 11 (Box 36)
      - Hankywood, Phoenix, AZ, 1996 May 9 (Box 36)
      - Money Magazine, Washington, D.C., 1996 May 20 (Box 36)
      - Duke Napa Event, 1996 May 16 (Box 36)
      - Bank of America, Pebble Beach, CA, 1996 5 15 (Box 36)
      - Hitachi Seminar, 1996 March 17-1996 March 21 (Box 36)
      - Merrill Lynch, Bahamas, 1996 March 2 (Box 36)
      - NAREIT, Florida, 1996 March 4 (Box 36)
      - U.S. News San Fran Trip, 1996 March 5 (Box 36)
      - National League of Cities, Washington, D.C., 1996 March 11 (Box 36)
      - Deloite and Touche, Chicago, 1996 April 2 (Box 36)
      - Mary Washington, Fredricksburg, VA, 1996 April 8 (Box 36)
      - Capital Guardian, Pancho Mirage, CA, 1996 April 24 (Box 36)
      - Jefferson Energy Program (Box 36)
      - CSSP, 1997 December 7 (Box 36)
      - Academy of Leadership (Box 36)
      - AOL Dinner (Box 36)
      - Spencer Stuart, Dallas and Houston, 1996 January 8-1996 January 9 (Box 36)
      - National Broiler Council, 1997 Octomber 10 (Box 36)
      - Bear Stearns, Beaver Creek, CO, 1996 January 13 (Box 36)
      - William Patterson, Wayne, NJ, 1996 January 26 (Box 36)
      - National Rural Electric, Opryland, 1996 February 7 (Box 36)
      - National Cotton Council, New Orleans, 1996 February 126 (Box 36)
      - Freightliner Corp, Portland, OR, 1996 July 16 (Box 36)
      - Past Calendar Items (Box 36)
    - Correspondence 1997, 5 Folders; folders 3-5 continue in Box 40
      - A-C (Box 36)
      - D-F (Box 36)
  - [Box #6] DRG Speeches1990-1991 (cont. from box 26) (Box 37)
    - DG Speeches:
      - NAC Re--1990 December 6-1990 December 7 (Box 37)
      - Education, Nat'l Alliance of Busi.: 1990 Octomber 3 (Box 37)
      - unspecified (Box 37)
    - Muhlenberg Comm. Address (Box 37)
    - DG Speeches, 1991 March 11, New Age Lecture, Am. Public Tran. (Box 37)
    - 1990 September: SET Speech (Box 37)
    - DG Speeches:
      - Shimoda (Box 37)
      - 1989 Standard Speech (Box 37)
    - Quinnipiac College Speech, 1990 May (Box 37)
    - DG Speeches, 1990 November, So. Center for Int'l Studies: Birmingham (Box 37)
    - West Virginia Wesleyan Addr. (Box 37)
    - DG Speeches
      - Investing in Europe, Georgetown Univ., Baltimore, October 3, 2 folders (Box 37)
      - 1987-1989 (Box 37)
      - Mo. Co. Public Schls: 1990 December 10 (Box 37)
      - Brookings: Public Policy, 1990 December 13 (Box 37)
      - Canadian Defense College: 1990 December 11 (Box 37)
      - NAC Re.--NYC, 1990 Decdember 6 (Box 37)
      - American Gas. Assoc., (USN), 1990 October 31 (Box 37)
      - Brookings Inst., 1991 February 27 Occidental (Box 37)
      - AEI--Osaka and Kyoto, 1990 November 18-1990 November 19 (Box 37)
  - [untitled box] (Box 37)
    - Christopher, Warren (Box 37)
    - Christopher--Speeches (Box 37)
    - Haiti--DG Notes (Box 37)
    - Potus Haiti Speech (Box 37)
    - Haiti (Box 37)
    - HC Speeches (Box 37)
    - Health Care plus NAFTA (Box 37)
    - Memorandum to interested parties (Box 37)
    - DG Clippings, 5 folders (Box 37)
    - Bosnia--DG, 2 folders (Box 37)
    - Crime--DG notes (Box 37)
    - DG Notes, crime bill (Box 37)
    - Health Care--DG notes (Box 37)
    - DG Notes--Health, Congress. Ldrs (Box 37)
    - DG Phone Book (Box 37)
    - Phone Logs 1995 September 9-1995 November 20 (Box 37)
    - DG Personal Notes, Letters (Box 37)
    - Thank Yous, 4 folders (Box 37)
  - [untitled box] (cont.) (Box 38)
    - Personal Notes (Box 38)
    - Media (Box 38)
    - POTUS (Box 38)
    - Wiley, Rein and Fielding (Box 38)
    - Clinton's Accomplishments (Box 38)
    - Ambrose, Steven (Box 38)
    - Steven Ambrose letter (Box 38)
    - Accomplishments, 3 folders (Box 38)
    - POTUS Administration Accomplishments (Box 38)
    - Memorandum for NEC principals (Box 38)
    - Cairo conference, 2 folders (Box 38)
  - SR-47 Gergen Info. Files (Box 38)
    - Editorials--other, 3 folders (Box 38)
    - EDSAT Institute (Box 38)
    - Education (Box 38)
    - Education: Nat'l Tests (Box 38)
    - Education Policy (Finn) (Box 38)
    - Education Spending (Box 38)
    - Eisenhower World Affairs Inst. (Box 38)
    - El Salvador (Box 38)
    - Empower America (Box 38)
    - Employment Wages (Box 38)
    - Energy (Box 38)
    - Environment, 2 folders (Box 38)
    - EESI (Environmental Energy Study Inst.), 2 folders (Box 38)
    - European Economy,1992 (Box 38)
    - European Security (Box 38)
    - Family Values (Box 38)
    - FCC (Box 38)
    - Foreign Affairs (Box 38)
    - Foreign Aid (Box 38)
    - Foreign Investment (Box 38)
    - Foreign Investment/Econ. (Box 38)
    - Foreign Policy (Box 38)
    - Foreign Policy: Sources (Box 38)
    - Foundations (Box 38)
    - Free Congress Foundation (Box 38)
    - Fun Facts (Box 38)
    - GATT Negotiations (Box 38)
    - Gergen lunchNovember 8 (Box 38)
    - David and Anne Gergen JT-Ten (Box 38)
    - Germany, 3 of 4 folders (Box 38)
  - SR-47 Gergen Info. Files (cont.) (Box 39)
    - Germany, 4 of 4 folders (Box 39)
    - Global Change Forum: The Stanley Found.--U.S. News Building Conf. Cent., September 21 (Box 39)
    - Gorbachev (Box 39)
    - Governmental Reform (Box 39)
    - Governors (Box 39)
    - Great Projects: Republican TV Show, 2 folders (Box 39)
    - Gulf War (Box 39)
    - Gun Control (Box 39)
    - Harvard (Box 39)
    - Health Care, 2 folders (Box 39)
    - Health Care Reform (Box 39)
    - Helsinki Commission (Box 39)
    - HMQ Piece (Health Mngmt.) (Box 39)
    - Hoover Institute (Box 39)
    - House (Congress) Bad Checks (Box 39)
    - House Wednesday GRP. (Box 39)
    - Hudson Institute (Box 39)
    - Human Rights (Box 39)
    - Hungary (Box 39)
    - IBM Exec Dev. Group (Box 39)
    - IBM Advanced Mngmt. Training (Box 39)
    - IISS Readings (Box 39)
    - Immigration, 3 folders (Box 39)
    - Inst. for Applied Economics (Box 39)
    - Institute for East-West Security Studies (Box 39)
    - Inst. for Int'l Economics (Box 39)
    - Inst. of Politics (Box 39)
    - Interaction Council (Box 39)
    - International Economy (Box 39)
    - International Media Fund, 4 folders (Box 39)
  - SR-47 Gergen Info. Files (cont.) (Box 40)
    - International Media Fund notebook (Box 40)
    - International Monetary Sys. (Box 40)
    - Investment (Box 40)
    - International Security (Box 40)
    - Iraq (Box 40)
    - Island Press (Box 40)
    - Japan, 5 folders (Box 40)
    - Japan Economic (Box 40)
    - Japan Society (Box 40)
    - Japan (Japan Society1991) (Box 40)
    - Japan Reading, 2 folders (Box 40)
    - Japan-US (Box 40)
    - Keating 5 (Box 40)
    - Korea (Box 40)
    - Labor Skills (Box 40)
    - Latin America (Box 40)
    - Law (Box 40)
    - Lawyers (Box 40)
    - Lobbying (Box 40)
    - Local Init. Support Corp. (Box 40)
    - The Monitor Channel (Box 40)
  - SR-48 Notes/Legal Pads and Reporter's Notebooks from Credenza (Box 40)
    - 34 Miscellaneous reporter's notebooks and 2 steno pads with notes (Box 40)
    - unspecified (Box 40)
  - SR-48 Notes/Legal Pads and Reporter's Notebooks from Credenza (cont.) (Box 41)
    - DG Speeches- 1991 October 1--PEPCO in DC--Washington Spkrs. Bureau (Box 41)
    - [Loose material], 2 folders (Box 41)
    - More Mutual/ M/L (Box 41)
    - Nat'l Cotton Council (Box 41)
  - Legal-sized material from box 50 (Box 41)
    - Innovation Awards
      - Democracy in Africa (Box 41)
      - Campaign Finance: Mitchell Interview (Box 41)
    - Legal-sized material from box 51
      - DG Appearances: M/L Show: Friday,1991 March 15, 2 folders (Box 41)
      - M/L Background (Box 41)
  - Legal-sized material from box 52 (Box 41)
    - PA and PAS Job Report (Box 41)
    - DG Speeches and Transcripts [Leadership Summit] (Box 41)
    - Clinton Admin. Speeches--Gergen DG Speeches (Box 41)
  - DRG 7 (Box 42)
    - Correspondence1997
      - G-L (Box 42)
      - M-N (Box 42)
      - O-Z (Box 42)
  - DRG 2 (Box 42)
    - Papers / Documents regarding the Reagan Administration (Box 42)
    - Loose Material
      - [Miscellaneous], 8 folders (Box 42)
      - [Reagan Tax Program], 5 folders (Box 42)
      - [Economics, Taxes, Budget], 6 folders (Box 42)
    - [Economic Recovery Tax Act of1981]
      - [Correspondence to Tom Evans] (Box 42)
      - Reagan Bi-partisan Tax Proposal,1981 July (Box 42)
      - [Surrogate Tax] (Box 42)
      - Background briefing for the cabinet on the president's tax program (Box 42)
  - [Box # 4] 1996: National Issues Convention; Debates; Congressional Debate; Primaries; GOP/Dem. Conventions; Character Above All; [all for MacNeil/Lehrer] (Box 43)
    - [Loose Materials: GOP Convention Budget] (Box 43)
    - [Loose Materials: DNC Convention Budget] (Box 43)
    - Budget: Character Above All (Box 43)
    - Character Above All Notes (Box 43)
    - AFPs: Character Above All
      - A-K (Box 43)
      - L-Z (Box 43)
    - Primary Budget (Box 43)
    - [Loose Material] (Box 43)
    - New Hampshire Primary
      - Notes, 1996 February 20 (Box 43)
      - AFPs (Box 43)
    - Super Tuesday1996 March 12
      - Notes (Box 43)
      - AFPs (Box 43)
    - [Loose material: Democratic National Convention Budget] (Box 43)
    - Set Design and Set, RNC, DNC (Box 43)
    - RNC Phones/Cellular Phones/Beepers Inst./Usage (Box 43)
    - RNC Computers (Box 43)
    - DNC Expense Reports (Box 43)
    - CO Studios RNC, DNC (Box 43)
    - RNC Remote Feeds/Trans. Pool--CBS (Box 43)
    - DNC Trailer/Workplace Furnishings/Supplies (Box 43)
    - Monitor Rental Tape Stock FL Crews (Box 43)
    - DNC Generator (Box 43)
    - DNC Makeup DAs Shields/Gigot (Box 43)
    - DNC Air, Hotels, Catering (Box 43)
    - DNC Travel Advances (Box 43)
    - DNC Taxi/ Shuttle Serv., Misc. Travel (Box 43)
    - DNC Computers (Box 43)
    - DNC Remote Feeds Transmission Pool Sub (Box 43)
    - DNC Phones/Cellular Phones/Beepers Inst./Usage (Box 43)
    - Contractors--DNC (Box 43)
    - Workplace--Skybox, Furnishings, Design, Supplies RNC (Box 43)
    - Hotel/Shuttle Bus/ Misc. Travel RNC (Box 43)
    - Desk Assistants Shields/Gigot RNC (Box 43)
    - Makeup, Security, Tape Stock RNC (Box 43)
    - FL Crew-Video Center, KPBS-Stage Crew, Screening Decks/Monitors AVW RNC (Box 43)
    - Contractors RNC (Box 43)
    - Notebook: The NEWSHOUR with Jim Lehrer, Republican National Convention1996 (Box 43)
    - Notebook: The NEWSHOUR with Jim Lehrer, Democratic National Convention1996 August 26-1996 August 29 (Box 43)
    - Travel Form: Convention Travel/Special Tickets (Box 43)
    - unspecified (Box 43)
    - Travel Form: Convention Travel/Special Tickets (Box 43)
    - San Diego:
      - Air Fares (Box 43)
      - Cash Advances (Box 43)
    - Chicago
      - Cash Advances (Box 43)
      - Air Fares (Box 43)
    - [Loose material: Republican Convention] (Box 43)
    - Presidential Inauguration1997 January 20 (Box 43)
    - Election Night 1996,1996 November 58pm-1am, 2 am update (Box 43)
  - [Box # 4], continued (Box 44)
    - Presidential Debate,1996 October 6, 9-11 pm (Box 44)
    - Vice-Presidential Debate,1996 October 9 (1 hr. show) (Box 44)
    - Presidential Debate,1996 October 16, 9-11 pm (Box 44)
    - [Loose Material], 2 folders (Box 44)
    - RNC--San Diego Budget (Box 44)
    - [Loose Materials] (Box 44)
    - WETA RNC, DNC1996 (Box 44)
    - DNC Chicago Budget (Box 44)
    - Budget National Issues Convention (Box 44)
    - NIC--BTL (Box 44)
    - Travel--E (Box 44)
    - American Express (Box 44)
    - Diners Club (Box 44)
    - Colorado Studios (Box 44)
    - National Issues Convention Notes (Box 44)
    - Journal Entries National Issues Convention (Box 44)
    - American Express Travel Arrangements (Box 44)
    - WETA (Box 44)
    - AFPs National Issues Convention
      - A-K (Box 44)
      - L-Z (Box 44)
  - [No SR #, no box label] (Box 44)
    - [Loose material: The Third Generation of Managed Care] (Box 44)
    - Dallas:1993 May 6 (Box 44)
    - American Assembly: Cities Program (Box 44)
    - 1993 April 27 (Box 44)
    - Palo Alto:1993 May 3 (Box 44)
    - [Loose materials: includes phone log April1993] (Box 44)
    - Notebook,1993 January-1993 February (Box 44)
    - Gergen (Box 44)
    - 1993 April 24: Tarrytown, NY (Box 44)
    - 1993 April 29: Chicago, IL (Box 44)
    - 1993 April 30: Lincoln, NE (Box 44)
    - Hefner--Christie (Box 44)
    - National Service, 3 of 4 folders (Box 44)
  - [No SR, no box label, cont.] (Box 45)
    - National Service, folder 4 of 4 (Box 45)
    - [Chicago:1993 April 29]? (Box 45)
    - Clinton 100 days (Box 45)
    - Plane tickets (Box 45)
  - [No SR, no box label (Box 45)
    - 1994 Christmas Card List (Box 45)
    - D-Day (Box 45)
    - Editorials by Gergen, 2 folders (Box 45)
    - Memos sent by Gergen (Box 45)
    - Professional Appointment Book (Box 45)
    - Finances (Box 45)
    - Financial (Box 45)
    - Independent Counsel, 2 folders (Box 45)
    - Privacy/White House - FBI Clips (Box 45)
    - Aspen Institute - Children and Families, 2 folders (Box 45)
    - Economies in Transition (Box 45)
    - Bilderberg Conference, in black binder and folder (Box 45)
  - [untitled box] (Box 46)
    - 1993 August (Box 46)
    - Clippings, 6 folders (Box 46)
    - Announcements (Box 46)
    - JAB -DG / UNC speech (Box 46)
    - Joe Fromm Memos (Box 46)
    - NAFTA - DG Notes (Box 46)
    - Birch Hayes (Box 46)
    - NED,1992 March 27 (Box 46)
    - Theatreworks (Box 46)
    - Faxes, 2 folders (Box 46)
    - Letter fromClinton (Box 46)
    - DG Media Appearances, 5 folders containing 8 photographs (Box 46)
    - [Subpoena for documents regarding Whitewater] (Box 46)
    - [Gergen's handwritten notes] (Box 46)
    - Health Care and Small Business (Box 46)
  - SR 3 (Box 47)
    - [Gergen's handwritten notes] (Box 47)
    - [Clippings], 2 folders (Box 47)
    - 22 Edit (Box 47)
    - Miami,May 23-May 24 (Box 47)
    - DG Speeches,1990 November-1991 February:
      - Changing Faces of Europe--Dickenson College: 1991 Febuary 17 (Box 47)
      - WSB: Pharm. Manu. Assn.: 1991 January 24 (Box 47)
      - Center for Nat'l Policy: 1991 January 23 (Box 47)
      - IIE: 1991 January 22 (Box 47)
    - DG Trips--Toyota Shimazu Lunch: NYC1991 January 14 (Box 47)
    - Center for Strategic and International Studies, Strengthening of America Meeting Folder (Box 47)
    - DG Speeches,1990 November-1991 February:
      - GWU Med. VIP's: Fri., 1990 December 7 (Box 47)
      - Comm. for Econ. Dev.: Thurs. 1990 November 8 (Box 47)
      - Edison Electric Inst.--Washington Campus: 1991 Febuary 21 (Box 47)
    - Georgetown Visitation (Box 47)
    - CSIS Panel Disc.:1991 January 29 (Box 47)
    - Trilateral Meeting (Box 47)
    - DG Speeches, Columbia University:1991 January. 29 (Box 47)
    - [Speeches/ Speech Notes], 3 folders (Box 47)
    - [Loose Material: Miscellaneous] (Box 47)
    - [Loose Material: Correspondence] (Box 47)
    - Political Sunspots: Washington Politics and August Weather (Box 47)
    - Serials:
      - Japan Echo, volume xv, number 2, Summer1988 (Box 47)
      - Television News Index and Abstracts, 1985 May (Box 47)
    - Notes, Scribbles, etc. (Box 47)
    - [1988taxes] (Box 47)
    - [Statements/Bills/Record of transactions] (Box 47)
    - Donations1988: A proposal for David Gergen (Box 47)
    - [USN Expenses Reimbursed] (Box 47)
    - [Dividends] (Box 47)
    - [Expenses Reimbursed--Non-USN] (Box 47)
    - [Media Appearances] (Box 47)
    - [Honorarium Check Copies] (Box 47)
    - [1988 Financial Information] (Box 47)
    - unspecified (Box 47)
  - SR 3 (cont.) (Box 48)
    - [Cancelled checks and Bank Statements]1988-1989, 4 folders (Box 48)
    - [Loose material], 4 folders (Box 48)
  - [No SR, no box title] (Box 48)
    - [11 audio tapes--primarily interviews1992--and 1 videotape were removed to Audio/Visual Materials box 55] (Box 48)
    - [Perot interview transcripts] (Box 48)
    - California (Box 48)
    - Campaign Coverage1992, 2 folders (Box 48)
    - The American Assembly, folder (Box 48)
    - [Loose material from The American Assembly folder] (Box 48)
    - Boston Mayor; WH/Mayors Meeting,1993 (Box 48)
    - The Lonely Days were Sundays(correspondence) (Box 48)
    - The Lonely Days were Sundays(draft) (Box 48)
    - Abortion (Box 48)
    - [Blue Binder materials] (Box 48)
  - [No SR, no box title] (cont.) (Box 49)
    - American Assembly (Box 49)
    - Untitled folder (Box 49)
    - 1992 NovemberElections (Box 49)
    - Towards a Reformulation of the Communications Act: A Report of the1993 Aspen Communications Forum (Box 49)
    - The Information Evolution: How New Information Technologies are Spurring Complex Patterns of Change (Box 49)
    - Competition at the Local Loop: Policies and Implications (Box 49)
    - US News and World Report--Gergen Stationary (Box 49)
    - CSIS, 2 folders (Box 49)
  - [No SR, MacNeil/Lehrer News Materials,1995] (Box 49)
    - Miscellaneous Notes (Box 49)
    - Untitled folder (Box 49)
    - DG Notes--PMA Mtg., Scottsdale, Arizona (Box 49)
    - 1989 November; American Assembly Speech/Background Material, Global Economy Workshop in Japan, 2 folders (Box 49)
    - Phillip Howard, Death of Common Sense, 2 folders (Box 49)
    - Kathleen Hall Jamison (Box 49)
    - Kitfield/ Military Reform (Box 49)
    - [Loose materials: Note that these materials were originally inside a Sutton Place Gourmet bag] (Box 49)
    - Kozol (DG Notes) (Box 49)
    - Rosabeth Moss Kanter (Box 49)
    - High Tide in Tucson promotional folder (Box 49)
    - Crime (Walinsky), 4 folders (Box 49)
    - Evan Thomas/CIA (Box 49)
    - [Loose material: Correspondence,1995] (Box 49)
    - Magazine List (Box 49)
    - Kozol/Amazing Grace, 2 folders (Box 49)
    - Francis Fukuyama (Box 49)
    - Michael Barone (Box 49)
    - Michael Lind (Box 49)
    - Donald/(Lincoln) (Box 49)
    - Wolff (Box 49)
  - [No SR, MacNeil/Lehrer News Materials,1995] (cont.) (Box 50)
    - Fukuyama (Box 50)
    - Baker (Box 50)
    - Goleman (Box 50)
    - 1995 April 1: WDC (Box 50)
    - [No SR, No box title] (Box 50)
    - [8 videocassettes removed to Audio/Visual Materials box 53] (Box 50)
    - New York State Decade of the Child Mentoring Program folder (Box 50)
    - [From unlabeled notebook] (Box 50)
    - RWJ Foundation 1995 April 27 (Box 50)
    - CBO Report on Health Care (Box 50)
    - Material from Seth Lerner (Box 50)
    - 1995 March 30: WDC (Box 50)
    - DC:1993 May 27 (Box 50)
    - DC:1993 May 5 (Box 50)
    - 1993 April 27: Palm Beach, Fla. (Box 50)
    - NED Dinner1993 April 27 (Box 50)
    - Beyond Rhetoric: A New American Agenda for Children and Families (Box 50)
    - [Brock Group] (Box 50)
    - [Loose material: Receipts and statements,1991] (Box 50)
    - National Commission on Children notebook (Box 50)
    - Out of Control: Global Turmoil on the Eve of the Twenty-First Century ( uncorrected advance proof), by Zbigniew Brzezinski (Box 50)
    - Raleigh/Durham:1995 May 15 (Box 50)
    - NYC:1993 May 17 (Box 50)
    - Wye River:1993 May 13-1993 May 14 (Box 50)
    - [Legal-sized material moved to box 41] (Box 50)
  - [No SR, no box title] (Box 50)
    - December 7 Edit Thinking for a Living (Box 50)
    - Bush Accomplishments (Box 50)
    - DG Editorial:1991 June 17 New American Order (Box 50)